[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":88098,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":400470,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":22472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":422945,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":6399,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":429349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":10742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":440093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":30870,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":470965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":12975,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":483942,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2860,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":486805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":9886,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":496692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":3360,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":500054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the s um is 6  or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":8709,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":508764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":3877,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":512644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":12975,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":525620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":3142,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":528764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":10530,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":539296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1723,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":541022,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Reme mber, to  perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":10819,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":551843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":3896,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":555740,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":11861,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":567603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1407,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":569012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":6072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":575085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1467,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":576555,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":36027,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":612588,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</s ub>). Si milarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":65222,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":677812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":28892,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":706706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6390,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":713099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the i nverse o f an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5966,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":719066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3406,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":722474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":728250,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1581,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":729833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":735985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2776,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":738762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</s ub>? <br  /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":7582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":746345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":9376,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":755722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes","response_history":["yes"],"rt":24358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":780082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":26397,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":806481,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 + <sub>6</ sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":128567,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":935049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":134531,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1069584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":13599,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1083184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":56845,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1140032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":11597,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1151631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":36423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1188055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":6149,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1194208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":18149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1212358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3471,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1215831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No I could not make out any relationships a mong par ticular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +6","response_history":["No I could not make out any relationships among particular subsets of the emel","No I could not make out any relationships among particular subsets of the eme","No I could not make out any relationships among particular subsets of the em","No I could not make out any relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under =","No I could not make out any relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under + ","No I could not make out any relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +6"],"rt":171349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1387182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except  now aft er adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19957,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1407141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1412247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1765,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1414014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1417326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1424958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1429125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1434070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1439949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, 4+1 = 5, five is lower than 9 so the answer is the sum of the numbers.","response_history":["5, 4=","5, 4+1 = 5, five is lower than 9 so it is the s","5, 4+1 = 5, five is lower than 9 so the answer is the sum of the numbers."],"rt":40829,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1480780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3, 8+4 =12 whic h is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for the answer, 12-9=3","response_history":["3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subr","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 f, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 fo, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for t, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for th, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for the, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for the , 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for the a, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for the ans, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so you must subtract 9 for the answe, 12-9=3","3, 8+4=12 which is greater than 9 so  you mus t subtract 9 for the answer, 12-9=3"],"rt":50633,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1531415,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, because when it is combined with anything it gives you that number back.","response_history":["o","0, because when it is combined with anything it gives you that number back."],"rt":230058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1761484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":36243,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1797730,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the in verse of  2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":5896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1803627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, because when combined with 3 in +9 the sum is 0 which would give you the identifier","response_history":["6, because when combined with 3 in p","6, because when combined with 3 in +9 the sum is 0 which would give you the identifier"],"rt":45742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1849371,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":" No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make all other numbers under +9","response_history":["No because it","No because i","No because the","No because th","No because t","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not ge","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make u","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make other nu","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make other n","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make other ","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make other","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make othe","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make oth","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make ot","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make o","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to  make all  other numbers under =","No because adding 2 together repeatedly does not give a way to make all other numbers under +9"],"rt":101926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1951298,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, you can't make the other numbers by using +9","response_history":["No, while you can make 0, ","No, while you can make 0,","No, while you can make 0","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, ","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4,","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, you can't make the other numbers with","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, you can't make the other numbers wit","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, you can't make the other numbers wi","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, you can't make the other numbers w","No, while you can make  6, 0, 4 , you can't make the other numbers ","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, you can't make the other numbers i","No, while you can make 6, 0, 4, you can't make the other numbers by using +9"],"rt":116373,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2067673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, while you can make 1 and 6 using +9, you can't make the other numbers.","response_history":["1, 6, ","No, while you can make 1, ","No, while you can make 1,","No, while you can make 1 and 6 using plu","No, while you can make 1 and 6 using pl","No, while you can make 1 and 6 using p","No, while you can make 1 and 6 using +9, you can't make the other numbers."],"rt":55740,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2123415,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13- 0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, while you can make 3 and 9, you can't make any of the other numbers.","response_history":["3, 9","N3, 9","No3, 9","No,3, 9","No, 3, 9","No, wh3, 9","No, whi3, 9","No, while3, 9","No, while 3, 9","No, while y3, 9","No, while you3, 9","No, while you c3, 9","No, while you can3, 9","No, while you can 3, 9","No, while you can m3, 9","No, while you can mak3, 9","No, while you can make3, 9","No, while you can make 3, 9","No, while you can make 3 9","No, while you can make 3 a 9","No, while you can make 3 an 9","No, while you can make 3 and 9. ","No, while you can make 3 and 9.","No, while you can make 3 and 9","No, while you can make 3 and 9, ou ","No, while you can make 3 and 9, ou","No, while you can make 3 and 9, o","No, while you can make 3 and 9, you can't make any of the other numbers."],"rt":66016,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2189432,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":42277,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2231712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+ +_n n","response_history":["1 =","1 +","1 ","1+ =","1+ +_n N","1+ +_n N","1+ +_n n"],"rt":398443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2630158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is t he formu la for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. ","response_history":["X +_n","X +_","X +","X ","X=","X+ +-","X+ +_nX","X+ +_n X, I got this answer bex","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be th eun","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be th eu","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be th e","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be th ","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element and this","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element and thi","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element and th","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element and t","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element and ","X+ +_n X, I got this answer b ecause X  would be the unknown element and","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element an","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element a","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element ","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This question confuses me but I","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This question c","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This question ","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This question","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This questio","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This questi","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This quest","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This ques","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknow n elemen t. This que","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This qu","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This q","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This ","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. This","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. Thi","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. Th","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. T","X+ +_n X, I got this answer because X would be the unknown element. "],"rt":155716,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2785877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really know what the element x is a generator under +_n without knowing if it can make all the elements.","response_history":["e","Generators are numbers when added together with the =","Generators are numbers when added together with the ","Generators are numbers when added together with the","Generators are numbers when added together with th","Generators are numbers when added together with t","Generators are numbers when added together with ","Generators are numbers when added together with","Generators are numbers when added together wit","Generators are numbers when added together wi","Generators are numbers when added together w","Generators are numbers when added together under =","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create t","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really  know wh at the element x is a generator un ","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really know what the element x is a generator under =","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really know what the element x is a generator under +-","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really know what the element x is a generator under +_n without knowing the ","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really know what the element x is a generator under +_n without knowing the","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really know what the element x is a generator under +_n without knowing th","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no  way to  really know what the element x is a generator under +_n without knowing t","Generators are numbers when added together under +n will create all other numbers. There is no way to really know what the element x is a generator under +_n without knowing if it can make all the elements."],"rt":96588,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2882467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":14509,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2896979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":13594,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2910575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":24922,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2935499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Because it would keep it from creating all other numbers when done with +_n","response_history":["True,","True","Tru","Tr","T","because for example if ","because for example if","because for example i","because for","because fo","because f","becaus e ","because","becaus","Because it would keep it from creating all other numbers when done with +-","Because it would keep it from creating all other numbers when done with +_n"],"rt":318380,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":3253881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":15403,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3269289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Because sometimes it would be able to create all other numbers depending on what n was.","response_history":["Because sometimes it would be able to create all other numbers depending on what n was."],"rt":102157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3371449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":29277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3400727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":4264,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3404993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"44","response_history":["44"],"rt":3030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3408024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Masters Degree","response_history":["Masters Degree"],"rt":3847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3411873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Beginning college algebra","response_history":["Beginning alger","Beginning algebrea","Beginning algebre","Beginning algebra","Beginning coalgebra","Beginning colalgebra","Beginning collealgebra","Beginning collegalgebra","Beginning collegealgebra","Beginning college algebra"],"rt":32451,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3444327,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":9334,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3453663,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":5817,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3459482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6909,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3466393,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":7481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3473878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":6279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3480159,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":3198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3483359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3490143,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":10734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3500879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"None.","response_history":["None."],"rt":4981,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3505863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]